A Guide to the Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.14-RG 1.15 (A88-A89) FA478
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.14-RG 1.15 (A88-A89)
1968-1991
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Foundation
FA478
55 Cubic Feet
Arrangement
Records are primarily arranged by Program.
Some subgroups may contain portions of the material that are arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1988-1989.
Scope and Contents
Types of records include: project and fellowship material.
Biographical / Historical
The Rockefeller Foundation was established by act of the New York State Legislature approved by the Governor on May 14, 1913, "to promote the well-being of mankind throughout the world." Between 1913 and 1928 the China Medical Board, the International Health Board, and the Division of Medical Education functioned as divisions of the Foundation, concentrating on the administration of programs in public health and medical education. A Division of Studies was created in 1923 to handle projects outside the medical field. These early years were experimental as the new foundation studied the methods of philanthropy and explored its relationships with other Rockefeller boards. Although the Rockefeller Foundation is the largest and best known philanthropy founded by the Rockefeller family, it was neither the first nor the last to be established. The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (1901), the General Education Board (1902), the Rockefeller Sanitary Commission for the Eradication of Hookworm Disease (1909), and the Bureau of Social Hygiene (1911) all existed earlier. When the Foundation was created, the Sanitary Commission was disbanded. After the establishment of the Foundation, the Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial (1918) and the International Education Board (1923) were created.
The Rockefeller boards and their programs were reconsidered and reorganized in 1927-1928 in order to avoid overlapping programs. The International Health Board of the Foundation was disbanded and an International Health Division was organized. The China Medical Board, Inc., was established as a separately incorporated institution, and the China Medical Board of the Foundation ceased to exist. The Division of Studies was dropped and the Division of Medical Education was phased out. The Laura Spelman Rockefeller Memorial was combined with the Foundation and the Spelman Fund of New York was chartered to continue activities of the LSRM that were not absorbed by the Foundation. The International Education Board was disbanded.
As a result of this reorganization, the Foundation adopted a program which included public health work (administered by the IHD), the advancement of knowledge in the medical and natural sciences (in part taken over from the IEB), the social sciences (formerly the field of the LSRM), and the humanities and arts (shared with the GEB). The Rockefeller Institute and the Bureau of Social Hygiene were not affected by the reorganization. The program adopted by the Foundation at this time remained basically the same for the next twenty years.
As its files accumulated, the Foundation maintained a card index recording the names of institutional and individual grantees and correspondents. A microfilm copy of this index is available at the Archive Center.
Conditions Governing Access
Records more than 20 years old are open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
Other Finding Aids
For other open RF project files, please refer to the following findng aids:
FA386 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.1
FA387 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.2
FA388 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3
FA209 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.3-1.8
FA479 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.9-1.13
FA469 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.16-1.19
FA477 Rockefeller Foundation records, projects, RG 1.25
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 88), 1963-1996; 1978-1987; 1.14; 10.12 Cubic Feet; 23 letter size document storage boxes (Boxes 1-23)
  Conditions Governing Access note
  Open for research with select materials restricted as noted. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC. Researchers interested in accessing digital media (floppy disks, CDs, DVDs, etc.) or audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
  Arrangement
  Arranged primarily by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure, with a small volume arranged by Program. Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1988.
  - Arts and Humanities (AH)
    - L.A. Theatre Works - Padua Hills Writers' Workshop (AH 8512), 1984-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS)
    - Oregon State University - Nitrogen Fixation Symposium (AS 8502), 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Equal Opportunity (EO)
    - Minority Rights Group - American Indians Study (EO 8506), 1984-1986 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Health Sciences (HS)
    - International Congress for Infectious Diseases - Infectious Diseases Control Colloquium (HS8501), 1984-1986 1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Measles Pathogenesis in Peru (HS8504), 1984-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5-6)
    - Infectious Diseases in the Tropics - Conference (HS 8508), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Basel Institute for Immunology - Immunology Symposium (HS 8510) (Rescinded), 1984-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - International Physicians for the Prevention of Nuclear War - Symposium (HS 8522), 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 9-10)
    - International Union of Immunological Societies - Immunology Symposium (HS 8524), 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - Roy M. Acheson (HS 8530), 1984-1986 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Yuan Hong-chang (HS 8534), 1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Chanpen Choprapawan (HS 8539), 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Gordon Research Conferences - Parasitism Conference (HS 8540), 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - American Society of Tropical Medicine & Hygiene - Catalog (HS 8550), 1984-1987 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - International Relations (IR)
    - Duke University - East-West Trade Conference (IR 8502), 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Georgetown University - Western Security, Defense, and Arms Control (IR 8504), 1983-1986, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 18-21, Box 4, Folder 22-24)
      General
      Folders 21-24 - Supplementary Material
      - "Toward a More Effective Defense", 2017:FA478:001 (Box 3, Folder 21)
        Conditions Governing Access
        Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact an archivist for further details.
    - Bretton Woods Committee (IR 8507), 1984-1986 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Catholic University of Leuven - European Security (IR8508), 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 26, Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Johns Hopkins University - Science, Technology, and Public Policy Conference (IR 8510), 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Harvard University - European Security (IR 8518), 1985-1986 (Box 5, Folder 29-31)
      Folders 30-31 - Supplementary Material
    - Council on Foreign Relations - African Lecture Series (David Rockefeller Lecturer) (IR 8528), 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Population Sciences (PS)
    - Virginia Commonwealth University - Singapore Population (PS 8505), 1984-1987 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Brown University - M. Kabir (PS 8514) (Rescinded), 1984-1985 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE)
    - Independent Sector - Studies in Leadership (SIE 8507), 1983-1989 (Box 6, Folder 35-37)
    - International Union of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences - Scientific Writing Conference (SIE 8510), 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 38)
    - International Association of Universities - Conference (SIE 8518), 1985-1986 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Medical Education for South African Blacks, Inc. - Evaluation of South African Facilities (SIE 8519), 1984-1986 (Box 7, Folder 40)
  - Rockefeller Foundation (RF)
    - Independent Sector - Fund for the Future (RF 85010), 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 41)
    - Marine Biological Laboratory - Gossypol and Echinoderm Sperm Motility (RF 85011) (A 35), 1985-1986, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 42)
  - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 175
    - J. A. Myers (175E), 1983-1986 (Box 7, Folder 43)
  - United States, 200
    - United States - Medical Sciences, 200
      - University of Hawaii - Dengue Studies (200A), 1984-1987 (Box 7, Folder 44)
      - University of North Carolina - Reproductive Biology (200A), 1971-1981 (Box 7, Folder 45-47)
      - University of North Carolina - Reproductive Biology (200A), 1968-1970 (Box 8, Folder 48-50)
        Folder 50 - Supplementary Material
      - Yale University - Antibody Detection (200A), 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 51)
    - United States - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, 200E
      - Gary E. Stack (200E), 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 52)
      - Gary E. Stack (200E), 1984-1987 (Box 8, Folder 52A)
        Closed material - Transcripts and Medical Information
    - United States - Humanities and Arts, 200R
      - Arts Policy Study (200R), 1984-1986 (Box 8, Folder 53)
      - Columbia University - Urban Folklore (200R), 1984-1987 (Box 9, Folder 54)
      - Educational Broadcasting Corporation - Films on Writing Instruction (200R), 1983-1986 (Box 9, Folder 55)
      - House Foundation for the Arts - Meredith Monk (200R), 1983-1987 (Box 9, Folder 56)
      - Hudson River Film and Video (200R), 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 57)
      - North Carolina School of the Arts - Visual Artists-in-Residence (200R), 1977-1984 (Box 9, Folder 58, Box 10, Folder 59-60)
        Folder 60 - Supplementary Material
      - Walker Art Center - Media Programs (200R), 1984-1986 (Box 10, Folder 61-62)
    - United States - Social Sciences, 200S
      - University of Chicago - Agricultural Economics (200S), 1963-1986 (Box 10, Folder 63, Box 11, Folder 64-68, Box 12, Folder 69-73, Box 13, Folder 74)
        Folders 63-64 - 1982-1986; Folders 65-67 - 1977-1981; Folders 68-69 - 1972-1976; Folder 70 - 1963, 1965-1966, 1968-1971; Folders 71-74 - Supplementary Material
  - Congressional Fellows Program, 288
    - American Philosophical Association (288), 1982-1983 1987 (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Brazil, 305
    - Brazil - University Development, UD
      - University of Bahia - Staff Development Awards, 1983-1984 (Box 13, Folder 76)
      - University of Bahia - Urban and Rural Education, 1980-1984 (Box 13, Folder 77-78)
      - University of Bahia - Urban and Rural Education, 1978-1979 (Box 13, Folder 79)
      - University of Bahia - Urban and Rural Education: Supplementary Material (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Colombia, 311
    - Protection of the World's Children/ Cartagena - Conference, 1985-1986 (Box 14, Folder 81)
    - Colombia - Medical Sciences, A
      - Universidad del Valle - Health Care Manual, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 82)
    - Colombia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Gustavo Correa, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 83)
      - Gustavo Correa, 1979-1981 (Box 14, Folder 83A)
  - Costa Rica, 313
    - Costa Rica - Medical Sciences, A
      - Demographic Association of Costa Rica - Health Statistics Monograph, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - England, 401
    - England - Medical Sciences, A
      - Mary Jane Cardosa, 1984-1986 (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Canada, 427
    - Canada - Medical Sciences, A
      - McMaster University - Health Care, 1981-1986 (Box 14, Folder 86, Box 15, Folder 87)
      - McMaster University - Health Care: Supplementary Material (Box 15, Folder 88-89)
      - University of Toronto - John R. Evans, 1978-1985 (Box 15, Folder 90-91)
      - University of Toronto - John R. Evans: Supplementary Material (Box 15, Folder 92)
    - Canada - Humanities and Arts, R
      - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation - International Screening Conference, 1983-1986 (Box 16, Folder 93-95)
      - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation - International Screening Conference, 1981-1982 (Box 16, Folder 96-97, Box 17, Folder 98)
      - Canadian Broadcasting Corporation - International Screening Conference: Supplementary Material (Box 17, Folder 99)
  - Jamaica, 437
    - Jamaica - Medical Sciences, A
      - University of the West Indies - Pediatric Trichuriasis, 1984-1987 (Box 17, Folder 100-101)
  - India, 464
    - India - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Shyamal Kumar Roy, 1982-1986 (Box 17, Folder 102)
      - Shyamal Kumar Roy, 1982-1986 (Box 17, Folder 102A)
  - Japan, 609
    - Japan - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Hiroshi Fujiwara, 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 103)
      - Hiroshi Fujiwara, 1982-1986 (Box 18, Folder 103A)
        Closed material - Medical Information
      - Horoshi Ueno, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 104)
      - Hiroshi Ueno, 1984-1986 (Box 18, Folder 104A)
        Closed material - Medical and Personal Information
      - Katsumi Yazaki, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 105)
      - Katsumi Yazaki, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 105A)
  - Korea, 613
    - Korea - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Inkyo Kim, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 106-107)
      - Inkyo Kim, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 107A)
        Closed material - Medical and Personal Information, Transcripts
      - Sun-Hee Lee, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 108)
      - Sun-Hee Lee, 1983-1986 (Box 18, Folder 108A)
  - Thailand, 617
    - Thailand - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Somsak Suthutvoravut, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 109)
      - Somsak Suthutvoravut, 1984-1985 (Box 19, Folder 109A)
  - Indonesia, 652
    - Indonesia - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Budi Winarno, 1980-1985 (Box 19, Folder 110)
      - Budi Winarno, 1980-1985 (Box 19, Folder 110A)
  - Israel, 825
    - Israel - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Boas Lev, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 111-112)
      - Boas Lev, 1980-1986 (Box 19, Folder 112A)
  - Special Interests and Explorations (SIE) (Interdisciplinary) - Biotechnology Career Fellowships, 860
    - Marcos Paiva (Rescinded), 1980-1985, 1991 (Box 19, Folder 113)
  - Program and Policy - Humanities, 911
    - Program and Policy - Humanities - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - Thomas Bender, 1983-1984, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 114)
      - Rosemarie Haag Bletter, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 115)
      - Joan Jacobs Brumberg, 1984-1986 (Box 19, Folder 116)
      - Mary Schmidt Campbell, 1983-1987 (Box 20, Folder 117)
      - Frederick Cooper, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 118)
      - Elinor Fuchs, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 119)
      - Richard Gillam, 1983-1986 (Box 20, Folder 120)
      - Dolores Greenberg, 1984 1986 (Box 20, Folder 121)
      - Margaret R. Higonnet, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 122)
      - Patrice L-R. Higonnet, 1984-1986 (Box 20, Folder 123)
      - Helen Lefkowitz Horowitz, 1982-1987 (Box 20, Folder 124)
      - Frederick E. Hoxie, 1982-1984, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 125)
      - Nathan I. Huggins, 1982-1984, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 126)
      - Peter W. Hylton, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 127)
      - Martin E. Jay, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 128)
      - T. J. Jackson Lears, 1983-1984, 1986-1987 (Box 21, Folder 129)
      - Sidney Monas, 1983-1984, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 130)
      - Thomas D. Moodie, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 131)
      - Jeffrey M. Perl, 1983-1984, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 132)
      - Moses Rischin, 1982-1986 (Box 21, Folder 133)
      - Phyllis Rose, 1983-1986, 1989 (Box 21, Folder 134)
      - Catherine Tinker, 1979-1981, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 135)
      - Richard S. Westfall, 1983-1986 (Box 21, Folder 136)
  - Program and Policy - Geographic Medicine, 928
    - Biomedical Research Center - Tropical Medicine, 1977-1987 (Box 22, Folder 137-139)
    - New England Medical Center - Immunoadjuvant, 1983-1984, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 140)
    - Program and Policy - Geographic Medicine - Fellowships, Scholarships, Training Awards, E
      - James W. Kazura, 1978-1985, 1987-1988 (Box 22, Folder 141-142)
      - Henry Wilke Murray, 1980-1987 (Box 23, Folder 143-144)
      - Rupert K. A. Schmidt-Ullrich, 1979-1987 (Box 23, Folder 145-147)
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A 89), 1973-1991; 1982-1988; 1.15; 44.84 Cubic Feet 37 standard record storage boxes (R2412-R2448) and 1 letter size document storage box (R2438A); Standard record storage boxes - Box R2412-Box R2448.
  Arranged primarily by Program, with a small volume of records arranged by the Rockefeller Foundation traditional series (country code) and subseries (program letter) structure.
  Records are arranged as received. Within folders, materials are primarily arranged in reverse chronological order.
  Open for research. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
  Project files transferred to the RAC by Rockefeller Foundation, 1989.
  - United States, 200
    Open for scholarly research, with prior archival review. Retrieval time may exceed 24 hours.
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents - Evaluation - (Abt Associates), 1982-1987 (Box 1, Folder 1-5, Box 2, Folder 6-10, Box 3, Folder 11-15, Box 4, Folder 16-20)
      Folders 1-4 - 1986-1987; Folders 5-11 - 1985; Folders 12-15 - 1984; Folders 16-18 - 1983; Folders 19-20 - 1982
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents - Evaluation (Abt Associates): Supplementary Material, 1973, 1979-1986 (Box 5, Folder 21-24, Box 6, Folder 25-29, Box 7, Folder 30-33, Box 8, Folder 34-37, Box 9, Folder 38-41, Box 10, Folder 42-47, Box 11, Folder 48-53, Box 12, Folder 54-55)
      Folders 21-28 - 1985-1986; Folders 29-33 - 1984; Folders 34-39 - 1983; Folders 40-47 - 1982; Folder 48 - 1982-1983; Folder 49 - 1985; Folder 50 - 1982-1985; Folder 51 - 1980-1981; Folder 52 - 1980; Folder 53 - 1979-1980; Folder 54 - 1979; Folder 55 - 1973, 1980
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents - Evaluation: Supplementary Material: Abt Associates, Inc.: Annual Report, 1983-1984 (Box 12, Folder 56-57)
      Folder 56 - 1983; Folder 57 - 1984
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents - Evaluation: Supplementary Material: Abt Associates, Inc.: Computer, 1983-1985 (Box 12, Folder 58-59)
      Folder 59 - Computers: Welfare of Women Meeting, June 12, 1984
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents - Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: Management Information System, 1982-1986 (Box 12, Folder 60, Box 13, Folder 61-67)
      Folder 60 - 1982; Folder 61 - 1983; Folder 62 - 1984; Folders 63-64 - 1985; Folder 65 - 1986; Folder 66 - Redesign of MIS; Folder 67 - Revisions to MIS Report
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents - Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: Survey, 1981-1985 (Box 14, Folder 68-73)
      Folder 68 - 1981; Folder 69 - 1982; Folder 70 - 1983; Folder 71 - 1984; Folders 72-73 - 1985
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents - Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: Implementation Analysis, 1984-1985 (Box 15, Folder 74-75)
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents - Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: Management/Contract: AAI-A/N, 1982-1984, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 76-79, Box 16, Folder 80-81)
      Folders 76-77 - 1982; Folder 78 - 1983; Folders 79-80 - 1984; Folder 81 - 1986
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents - Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: Impact: AAI-RDS, 1982-1984 (Box 16, Folder 82-85)
      Folder 82 - 1982; Folder 83 - 1983; Folders 84-85 - 1984
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: Impact, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 86, Box 17, Folder 87)
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: Annual Work Plans, 1982-1986 (Box 17, Folder 88-93)
      Folder 88 - AAI 1982; Folder 89 - AAI 1983; Folder 90 - AAI 1984; Folders 91-92 - AAI 1985; Folder 93 - 1986
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: Cost-Benefit Analysis, 1983-1985 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: Advisory Committee, 1981-1987 (Box 18, Folder 95-102, Box 19, Folder 103-105)
      Folder 95 - Members, Vitae; Folder 96 - 1982-1983; Folder 97 - Meetings 1983; Folder 98 - Reports 1983; Folder 99 - 1984; Folders 100-101 - Meetings 1984; Folder 102 - Reports 1984; Folder 103 - 1985; Folder 104 - Meetings 1985; Folder 105 - General Correspondence 1986-1987
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: Community-Based Organizations, 1983-1985 (Box 19, Folder 106-110)
      Folders 106-107 - 1983; Folders 108-109 - 1984; Folder 110 - 1985
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: Telephone Conversations, 1984-1985 (Box 20, Folder 111-112)
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: AAI Monthly Progress Reports, 1982-1986 (Box 20, Folder 113-116, Box 21, Folder 117-120)
      Folder 113 - 1982; Folder 114 - 1983; Folder 115 - 1984; Folders 116-118 - 1985; Folders 119-120 - 1986
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: AAI Invoices, 1984-1987 (Box 21, Folder 121)
    - Employment Program for Minority-Group Female Single Parents Evaluation: Abt Associates, Inc.: Supplementary Material: Guide to the MFSP Evaluation Data Base, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 122, Box 22, Folder 123-126)
      Folder 122 - Draft; Folders 123-124 - Abt Data Base-Original
  - Arts and Humanities (AH)
    - National Humanities Center - American History Teachers (AH 8505), 1983-1986 (Box 23, Folder 127-128)
    - George Washington University - Humanities and Public Policy (AH 8506), 1985-1987 (Box 23, Folder 129)
    - Painted Bride Art Center - Beck Troupe (AH 8509), 1984-1987 (Box 23, Folder 130-131)
    - Children's Museum (Boston) - Cross-Cultural Programming (AH 8513), 1983-1989 (Box 24, Folder 132-133)
    - Exploratorium - Artists-in-Residence (AH 8515), 1982-1987 (Box 24, Folder 134-136)
      - Slides (20), 2017:FA478:002 (Box 24, Folder 136)
        Separated Materials
        20 slides separated for preservation concern
    - University of Maryland - Shakespeare Teachers Institute (AH 8516), 1984-1987 (Box 25, Folder 137-139, Box 26, Folder 140-142)